This is Ranma from
the Saotome School
of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
Our dear Ranma here has
a bit of a problem.
He transforms into a girl
when splashed with cold water.
RANMA1/2
HOT COMPETITION
Attacking
with your bare hands is forbidden
in Martial Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics.
The match is tomorrow.
The only way for you
to master every technique is practice.
Hmm.
Have you prepared yourself?
The real question is
are you ready for this?
I want you to come at me from any dir--
Ha! Too eas--
What are you, an animal?
Use the tools I gave you.
Huh.
Yeah, you're really annoying.
Okay, let's try this again!
Hmm? Hmm.
Oh.
WORM - DOG
TWERP - LOSER
Wow. You're pretty good at this, Ranma.
I know.
I wasn't just hanging out
when I spent the whole week with you--
What the heck!
Ranma, are you okay?
Lay down and get some rest.
I can't just go and take a nap.
Why? You're not getting worried
about me, are you?
As if. You know that's not what I meant.
Please rest. And, no,
you don't have to worry.
I'll be making sure
he learns my secret techniques properly.
Really?
Well, if he keeps going at this
pace he'll win without breaking a sweat.
Hold on.
Where did P-chan run off to?
I happened
to hear something earlier.
If you lose the match tomorrow,
then you have implicitly agreed
to give yourself over
to Kodachi, the Black Rose, as her prize.
Yeah.
In other words, you'll be forced into
breaking off your relationship with Akane.
So I expect you
to do what you can to lose, Ranma!
Hmph. I did think it was strange
you were so interested in coaching me.
I knew you weren't just doing it
to be nice.
Sorry to tell you this, but I have
no intention of dating that woman.
Good luck standing
when your legs are broken.
Go ahead. I'd like to see you try!
I slept so well.
And the weather's perfect.
Mmm.
Uh...
What's going on? What are you doing?
There! Had enough?
I'm not done yet.
Wha... Have you two been at it
all night long?
It's morning already?
Hey, uh, are you doing okay?
I'm fine, just fine.
I'm doing so good.
- Kasumi.
- Hmm?
This fish cake's very tough.
- 'Cause that's a towel, dear.
- Oh, okay.
H-He's out of it.
Pardon the interruption. There will be
a Martial Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics
match held later today at 1:00 p.m...
You want to play your substitution?
Yes. I got injured yesterday.
She'll be the one taking my place.
Oh, yes. The girl with the pigtail.
I believe she and I have met before.
Very well, then.
To a good match,
and may the best woman win.
Mm-hmm.
Oh! Now how did
all those little tacks get there?
FURINKAN HIGH SCHOOL
This is the place.
Look out!
You can't let your guard down
for a second.
I'm awake now.
Mmm? Huh?
GOOD LUCK
FROM THE BLACK ROSE
Hmm?
Must be sleeping pills.
This is St. Bacchus' School
for Girls, right?
Please tell me this is the place.
Uh, yeah.
I can't believe I got here
without getting lost.
- What is that guy's problem?
- Mm-mmm.
I never had a sense of direction before,
but I made it all the way here in one go!
That proves
the power of love. Akane!
Now isn't the time
for me to stand around and cry.
I came here because I wanted
to mess up Ranma's fight--
Watch it! What if there was
a person down there?
It's okay. It's just a little piggy.
I've done what I can,
but I still need to land the final blow.
I have to secure the win
so I may date Lord Ranma.
Hmm?
- You're so cute!
- Oh!
Oh! I wanna hold it next.
Where do you guys think
this piggy came from?
- Oh! Kodachi.
- Huh?
Perhaps I know of a way
for this little piggy to be of use.
Thank you
to the ten million fans
that have tuned in
to this broadcast nationwide!
The Martial Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics match
between Furinkan High School
and St. Bacchus' School for Girls
will be kicking off at any moment.
Now we ask that you turn your eyes
to the entrance.
The school representatives are coming in!
Kodachi, the Black Rose,
is the first to enter the spotlight.
A halo of light surrounds her frame
like a goddess.
Furinkan High School is heading
toward the other corner.
Furinkan's player was injured
and requested a last-second replacement,
so the school will be represented
by the beautiful and mysterious woman
coming into the ring.
We can hear the crowd's excitement
swelling into a boil
as they begin to chant Kodachi's name.
The mystery girl shows
incredible concentration,
even while competing away from home.
I am really looking forward to this one!
Kodachi! Kodachi!
Hello, elder brother.
Ah. Hello there.
- It's Kodachi's brother!
- He's hot!
And so cool.
Is he, though? Well,
I guess it's better if I don't get it.
You got that right.
In the Red Corner...
Kodachi Kuno!
Blue Corner...
Oh, oh, sorry. What's your name again?
Ranma Saotome.
You're giving them your real name?
Oh, it'll be fine.
Representing
Furinkan High School...
...Ranma Saotome!
Ranma Saotome?
Uh, wait. It's the pigtailed girl.
- Her name is Ranma Saotome?
- Ranma?
- Well do they have the same name?
- That's weird, right?
That girl's name
is Ranma Saotome, is it?
So she would dare to have
the same name as my lord?
That's really, really, really annoying.
At last I know her true name!
I'd better write it down
so as not to forget.
Well, all right, then.
They just have the same name.
I mean, that might be it.
But she kinda looks like him.
Lots of people look similar
to each other, man.
See?
Fighters, come to the center.
Okay! Please shake hands
when you're ready.
- What's that over there?
- Huh?
Uh...
- Hmm.
It was a mistake
to let your guard down.
Hmm.
P-chan?
What is it with you
always getting in the way?
You're gonna pay, Ryoga.
The ring of the bell has
already been drowned out
by the deafening roars of this crowd.
This single-round, no-holds-barred match
has now begun.
Bringing you live commentary,
you know and love the team,
it's Ichiro and the
Furinkan High School Radio Club.
Furinkan?
Is it just me, or are they everywhere?
The contenders are not allowed
to strike with bare hands.
It will end only when
one of them is knocked down for good.
The rules also state
that falling out of the ring
results in immediate disqualification.
All right, Ryoga. Cause me trouble
and I'm eating ham tonight.
Can't really say
I'm a big fan of hitting girls.
I'll push you out of the ring
before I even need to hit you!
How charming of you to be so considerate.
Fantastic rope-handling!
We should expect nothing less
from the sport's flower, Kodachi Kuno!
Uh...
Hang on. What is that? A pole?
It's a pole that looks like a rope!
Come on, ref! Those aren't legal.
They are. Using tools is safe.
Huh?
Kodachi's switching
to the club now.
She's throwing out a barrage of strikes!
Wait! Did she put spikes
all over the end of that club?
I'm not seeing anything on 'em.
Did she get custom-made clubs
with a built-in button for spikes?
She may be my sister,
but that is brilliantly sneaky.
I do it all in the pursuit
of dating Lord Ranma Saotome.
Yes, I'm an unbelievably tragic
and brave heroine.
Don't be ridiculous!
That's funny. So, I'm curious.
When do I get a say in this?
'Cause I don't wanna date you!
- Pig. Legal!
Ranma Saotome executes
a perfect pig attack!
Its use as a tool has been approved.
Who said anything about dating you?
What a fool.
Yeah, whatever.
If you lose, you need to stop bugging
both the Ranma Saotomes. Hear me?
Hmm?
And who exactly are you
when it comes to our Lord Ranma?
Are you leaving us alone or not? Huh?
Wh-What are you doing?
So you must be in love
with Lord Ranma as well.
Is that why you're determined
to keep getting in the way?
Now what kind of woman are you?
Good luck dodging any of this!
He already said he doesn't like you.
I shall soon be exposing that lie.
- Hoop, now.
- Here!
An insolent woman does not deserve
to say my lord's name.
Fall back and accept your judgment
from the Black Rose!
The hoop is in the air!
Is that a razor?
Well done!
She narrowly avoided a ribbon strike.
But our goddess of war isn't done yet.
Ranma dodges it like an expert with a stag
jump stacked on top of an open leg jump.
Fantastic defense!
Ranma!
If you're not gonna get it
the first time I say it,
I'm just gonna have
to make you understand!
Amazing!
She turned her pole into nunchucks!
Hmm. This is so absurd.
You've given me no choice
but to utilise
the Black Rose's secret move.
Feel my Attack of One Thousand Hand Clubs!
Oh, no! Then her Thousand Arms
seem to have manifested before us
in the center of the ring!
I believe I can make out
at least ten or 20 clubs.
Ranma!
Attack!
Whoa!
Upon further inspection,...
...it appears that Kodachi Kuno was
only able to utilise that move
by using ten to 20 clubs!
That is beyond super sneaky!
Keep watching.
The essence of
Martial Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics
is evolving our use of tools!
Huh?
Hmph.
- A deadly attack with the bell!
- Uh-oh!
Ranma Saotome blocks it with the pig!
That piggy is squealing right now.
He's probably telling our contender
that she's lost her mind!
Uh, what else was I supposed to do?
- Now's my chance!
- Oh, crap!
It's my turn.
Ranma's grabbed the announcer's table!
Like the Tosa fishers of old,
she cast a single line to snatch our table
and make it dance through the air!
Undaunted, Kodachi wraps up
and reels in her brother!
Naturally, any biological brother is
considered a tool.
Human brother. Legal!
- Legal!
We are now existing
in a lawless hellscape!
But maybe it would be more accurate
to call it a battle wonderland!
Mr. Saotome. Oh.
Now is not the time for us
to be sitting around and drinking tea.
Well, you certainly are
a tenacious woman.
For such a dogged match...
This would fell even a cockroach!
Boiling Water Attack!
Saotome can't cope with the heat
and backs off.
Perfectly reasonable
to want to avoid scalding water.
You didn't seem to enjoy that very much.
If I turn back into a guy
dressed like this...
I'm not getting hit with that!
Saotome has escaped into the air,
but Kuno won't let her get away.
Nice try!
UH-OH!
What was that?
Ranma Saotome has just taken
a direct hit of boiling water!
Do you think it hurt?
Hmm? What's that?
There, in the steam... Are there two people?
Nice outfit you got on, Ranma.
It's better than being completely naked.
You dummy!
What's this?
It looks like Saotome's
second has busted out the fire hose.
Oh, I guess it was
just the girl and the pig.
Must have been
an optical illusion.
- Oh, thank goodness.
- Whoa!
Oh, no!
At this rate, she might get pushed
out of the ring!
Which, as we know, would mean
instant disqualification.
Looks like it's all over for Saotome.
No way! Saotome is trying
to swim back to the middle of the ring.
This is tenacity that defies common sense.
So she enlisted help from her second.
How very sneaky.
What the...
Give up this pointless struggle.
You wish to steal Lord Ranma
from me that badly?
Excuse me?
When exactly did he agree to be yours?
I refuse to argue.
This is annoying.
Get out of the ring already!
Whoa! No!
This time it's Kodachi Kuno
who's flying out of the ring.
Whoa!
Huh?
Huh. Did the ring just move?
You'll never be able to push me
out of this ring.
I know your game.
There we go. The ring was moved
using a group of people hidden beneath it.
Members of
the St. Bacchus' School for Girls'
Martial Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics Team
frantically leave the ring.
And, uh,
now that the mat has been demolished,
the only remaining footholds are
the corner posts and ropes.
Falling off them would mean a loss.
Good thing aerial combat is key to our
School of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
Come on! Let's put an end to this!
You're so impudent!
Ryoga!
Razor hoop!
All right, you dunderhead.
If you ever dare to get in my way again,
I will rip your little pig body to shreds.
For some reason, Saotome has started
boorishly bullying the pig!
But that careless mistake allowed Kodachi
to catch Ranma off guard.
Seems as though she'll land
right in the middle of the ring!
No, she's not down-and-out yet.
What stunning tenacity from Saotome.
Okay, time for me to take you down!
Uh-oh. She's swinging back
like a pendulum.
Well that certainly is a shame, isn't it?
Let's end this!
She's using the recoil
from the rope to launch herself.
But will she make it this time?
You're such a fool.
Did you forget you can't attack me
without a weapon?
The only weapon I need is
the one you're standing on!
Oh! Kodachi Kuno has fallen
outside of the ring!
That's it. The winner is Ranma Saotome!
Total defeat.
Whoo! Ranma!
Just as I promised you, I shall
throw the feelings I had to the side.
All those burning feelings of desire.
Kodachi.
Oh.
I've come to a decision.
At tomorrow's new dawn,
I shall burn for Lord Ranma
with a new and unique fervor!
Lord Ranma!
We admire the persistence
of your fighting spirit, Kodachi Kuno!
We'd want nothing less for our
blossoming black rose of the ring.
She's all burned out.